Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS 180 MSS 180
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Committed (1984)
  Series IV: Committed contains papers, images, and other materials related to the creation and distribution of the film "Committed". These materials include annotated drafts of the screenplay, film stills, newspapers articles and reviews, etc. This series is divided into two subseries:
  A: Drafts and Production
  B: Publicity and Distribution
  - Series IV, Subseries A: Drafts and Production
    - Committed: An Original Screenplay, Undated (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Committed Artwork - Large format B&W negative, Undated (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Committed - B&W Contact sheets, Undated (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Committed - B&W movie stills (1 of 2), Undated (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Committed - B&W negatives (large formats and regular), films, stills, Undated (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Committed Press, Undated (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Committed - B&W Stills (2 of 2), Undated (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Committed - French translation by Bernice Reynaud, Undated (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Committed - German Translation by Dirk Zimmer and David Rattray, Undated (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Committed - Institutional support: financial and exhibition, Undated (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Committed - miscellaneous administration, Undated (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - Committed - Slides and Negatives, Undated (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - Frances Farmer Script - Original, Undated (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - Notes and Script Drafts, Undated (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Research copy of envelope and phone list / sequence, Undated (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Series IV, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution
    - Claudia Tronnier Interviews Sheila McLaughlin and Lynne Tillman (German Language publication), Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Committed, Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Committed: Film Festival in Australia, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Committed: Film Festival reviews (Portuguese), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Committed: Film Festival reviews (Dutch, German, French, Italian), Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Committed: Film Festival Taiwan, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Committed: Film Festival USA, 1984-1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Committed - Press and Publicity, Undated; Unknown (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Committed - Press and Publicity (English), Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Committed - Prina and Williams interview Lynne Tillman and Sheila McLaughlin, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Committed Publicity, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Committed Publicity, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Committed Publicity, Undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Edinbourgh International Film Festival Program, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Essay: "Committed: Feminist Spectatorship and the Logic of the Supplement", Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Hallways - Screening of Committed, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Lynne Tillman article on Sheila McLaughlin - annotated typescripts, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Series V: Haunted Houses (1987)
  Series V: Haunted Houses contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "Haunted Houses". This series includes drafts of the book and publicity and reviews in newspapers and magazines. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series V, Subseries A: Drafts and Production
    - 2nd draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - 3rd draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Annotated draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Annotated draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Annotated draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Annotated draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Annotated draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Annotated draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Annotated draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Annotated draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Annotated draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Annotated draft - Emily chapter 3, Undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Annotated draft from Part 5, Undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Annotated draft - Grace, Undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Annotated draft - Green pages, Jane, Undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Annotated draft - Jane, Undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Annotated draft - Jane, Undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Annotated draft, notes, Undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Annotated draft, notes, Undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Annotated draft, notes, fragments - Emily chapter 4, Undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Annotated draft, notes, fragments - Grace chapter 3, Undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Annotated draft, notes, fragments - Jane chapter 4, Undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Annotated draft pages - Various, Undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Annotated draft pages 10-15. 19-22, Undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Annotated draft, pink pages - Jane, Undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Annotated Final Draft (1 of 2), Undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Annotated Final Draft (2 of 2), Undated (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Annotated folder - Grace chapter 4, Undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Draft - Jane, Undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Early writing, Undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Emily chapter 1 - annotated, Undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Fragments - pages 25, 27, 28, Undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - High Risk cover proofs, Undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - "Insert A" annotated, cut and tape, Undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Jane and Grace chapter 1 draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Multicolored annotated draft, Emily, Undated (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Multicolored annotated draft, Emily, Undated (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Notes for Emily and Jane (1st chapter), Undated (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Photocopies of annotated drafts, Undated (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Photocopy of annotated draft, Undated (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Photocopy of annotated draft - Jane, Undated (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Poseidon page proof, Undated (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Source Material - notes and drafts, Undated (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Series V, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution
    - Excerpt published in unknown magazine, Undated (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Kathy Acker's quote on Haunted Houses, Undated (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - "Keeping People Warm" - Robert Clark review of Haunted Houses; with a postcard from Lynne Tillman, Undated (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Lynne Tillman Haunted Houses publicity, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Mentions in publications, Undated (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Newspaper mentions, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Press for Haunted Houses, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Publicity, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Reviews, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Reviews and Publicity (English, Spanish, German), Undated (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Reviews (Robert Gluck), Undated (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Second Shift - "Like Mother, Like Daughter" extract, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 74)
- Series VI: Motion Sickness (1991)
  Series VI: Motion Sickness contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "Motion Sickness". This series includes annotated drafts of the book and mentions, publicity, and reviews in newspapers and magazines. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series VI, Subseries A: Drafts and Production
    - Annotated chapters 1-7, Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Annotated chapters 7-12, Undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Annotated chapters 13-end, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Annotated page proofs (1 of 2), Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Annotated page proofs (2 of 2), Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Excerpt from "Homesick" - annotated original, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - HSK / Australians / etc..., Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Michel Delsol envelope contents (1 of 4), Undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Michel Delsol envelope contents (2 of 4), Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Michel Delsol envelope contents (3 of 4), Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Michel Delsol envelope contents (4 of 4), Undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Uncorrected Proof, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Series VI, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution
    - Motion Sickness and Absence Makes the Heart Review, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Press, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Press and Publicity, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Press and Publicity, Undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Required Reading - for Postmodernism and comtemporary culture with Prof. Thomas Keenan, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Review, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Review, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Review - German Press, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Series VII: Cast in Doubt (1992)
  Series VII: Cast in Doubt contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "Cast in Doubt". This series includes annotated drafts of the book, cover art, the press release, and publicity and reviews in newspapers and magazines. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series VII, Subseries A: Drafts and Production
    - Annotated original manuscript (1 of 2), Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Annotated original manuscript (2 of 2), Undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Articles: Politics and Art, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Bob Siegle internet conversation, Undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Cast in Doubt - Advance uncorrected proof, Undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Chapters 1-5, annotated, Undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Chapters 1-5 (1 of 2), Undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Chapters 6-11, annotated, Undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Chapters 6-12 (2 of 2), Undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Chapters 12-end, annotated, Undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Chapter 16 - Helen's Diary, Undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Chapter 17 #6 - Coda, the Rough Future, Undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Chapter 17 #7 - Coda, the Rough Future, Undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Chapter 17 #7 - Coda - The Rough Future, Undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Coda, Undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Color Copy of Artwork for cover, Undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Copies and Page proofs with annotations, Undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Copy Edited and Final Version chapters 1-6 (1 of 3), Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Copy Edited and Final Version chapters 7-13 (2 of 3), Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Copy Edited and Final Version chapters 14-end and notes (3 of 3), Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Cover Negative, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Cover Proof with corrections, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Draft - chapters 1-5 annotated, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Draft - chapters 6-12, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Draft - chapters 13-coda, Undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Draft I - Fonda's corrections chapters 1-6, Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Draft I - Fonda's corrections chapters 7-12, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Draft I - Fonda's corrections chapters 13-coda, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Draft III - chapters 1-6, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Draft III - chapters 7-13, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Draft III - chapters 14-Coda, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Draft folder - labeled Crete, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Helen's Diary - chapter 16 #6, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Memorandum of Agreements, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Microfilm copies - activities in New York Theater, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Notes, annotated work copy, edits, Undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Notes, newsclippings, D. Dean letter, Undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Paperback cover with note from Fonda Duvanel, Undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Publisher letter, Undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Timeline, Undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Series VII, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution
    - Press and Publicity, Undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Press Release, Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Promotional agenda, Undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Publicity, Undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Publicity, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Reviews, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Reviews, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Reviews, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Reviews, Undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Reviews, Undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Serpent's Tail Promotion folder, Undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Tour - Mind King program, resume, Undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Series VIII: The Velvet Years (1995)
  Series VIII: The Velvet Years contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "The Velvet Years". This series includes research for the book, writing fragments, interviews collected by Lynne Tillman, and publicity through magazines and newspapers. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series VIII, Subseries A: Drafts and Production
    - American Center - Warhol Film and Television; War Without Enemies, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Callie Angel's Warhol exhibition, Undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Contemporary newspaper articles - research, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Copies of pictures - not needed (1 of 2), Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Copies of pictures - not needed (2 of 2), Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Letters and correspondence - research, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Map and captions; editing comments, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Notes and fragments, Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Pavillion, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Photocopied pages from "The Autobiography and Sex Life of Andy Warhol", Undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Raw material - Warhol, the Velvets, and the Factory (Annotated), 1994 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Reflections on Andy Warhol (various people), Undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Research materials for "The Velvet Years", Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Research - newspaper articles and notes, Undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Warhol Box by David Dalton, Undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Warhol Files - notes, contacts, notecards, letters, and transcript fragments, Undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Whitney Museum - "The Films of Andy Warhol, Part II", Undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Writing fragments, annotated, Undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Series VIII, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution
    - Book Receipt, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Billy Name, Undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Danny Fields, Undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Donald Lyons, Undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Gerard Malanga, Undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Gordon Baldwin, Undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews John Ashberry, Undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews John Cale, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Jonas Mekas, Undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Mary Woronov, Undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Maureen Tucker, Undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Pat Hatley, Undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Paul Morrisey, Undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Sam Green, Undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Stephen Shore, Undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Stephen Shore, Undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Sterling Morrison, Undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Susan Bottomly, Undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Lynne Tillman interviews Taylor Mead, Undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Mentions, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Press and Publicity, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Press and Publicity, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Promotional Photographs, Undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Review, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Reviews, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Reviews and Mentions, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Transcript of Tillman interview with Henry Geldzanler, Undated (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Transcript of Tillman interviews with Ultra Violet, Undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Series IX: No Lease on Life (1997)
  Series IX: No Lease on Life contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "No Lease on Life". This series includes annotated and edited drafts of the book, and reviews and publicity in newspapers and magazines. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series IX, Subseries A: Drafts and Production
    - Annotated uncorrected proof, Undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Draft, Undated (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Draft, Undated (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Draft - labeled pages 1-5, Undated (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Draft (1 of 2), Undated (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Draft (2 of 2), Undated (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Draft (1 of 2), Undated (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Draft (2 of 2), Undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Draft (1 of 2), Undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Draft (2 of 2), Undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Draft (1 of 2), Undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Draft (2 of 2), Undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Draft "Elizabeth 6A pages 49-62", Undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Draft "From Elizabeth 6A", Undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Draft fragment, Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Draft fragments, planning, Manhattan transit, Undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Draft and Notes, Undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Edited Copy from Publisher (1 of 2), Undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Edited Copy from Publisher (2 of 2), Undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Elizabeth draft, Undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Elizabeth - newspaper clippings, Undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Form for Jacket Flaps and Verso, Undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Frank's notes, Undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Matchbook jacket with text, Undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - "Next to Nothing" for Laconian Inc., 1996 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Original Draft (1 of 2), Undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Original Draft (2 of 2), Undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Part 1 of 2 (Draft), Undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Part 2 of 2 (Draft), Undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - "Reckless Disregard", Undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Short - "For Aperture", Undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Uncorrected Book Proof, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Uncorrected Book Proof, Undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Series IX, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution
    - "Die Mieteren" - German Press, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - English publicity and press, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - German Press, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Manhattan Bus map, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - New York - events, publicity, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - No Lease on Life and Bookstore, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - On the writing of "No Lease on Life", Undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Paperback publication announcement, Undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Press, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Press, Undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Press, Undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Promotional Tour (Portland, Seattle, Oakland, Los Angeles, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Publicity, Undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Publicity, Undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Publicity contacts and Bio materials, Undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Reviews, 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Reviews and Publicity, 1997-2005 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Series X: Bookstore (1999)
  Series X: Bookstore contains materials related to the creation and distibution of Lynne Tillman's book "Bookstore". This series includes research, annotated drafts of the book, and press and reviews in newspapers and magazines, including the Books & Co. "Off the Wall" newsletter. The series is divided into two subseries:
  - Series X, Subseries A: Drafts and Production
    - Annotated Uncorrected Proof, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Books & Co. Editing Notes, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Books & Co. Farewell Mailing, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Books & Co. - Lynne Tillman Research and News Stories, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Books & Co. - Rebecca's Research, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Covers, Captions, and Images, Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Draft Comments, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Edited Manuscript pages 1-118 (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Edited Manuscript pages 119-237 (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Edits and Changes; Permissions and Comment Drafts, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - First Draft with J. Watson's Annotations (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - First Draft with J. Watson's Annotations (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Harcourt Brace and Co. Dust Jacket, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Index Draft, Undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Interview Releases and Consent Forms for "Bookstore: The Life and Times of Jeannette Watson and Books & Co., 1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Jeannette Watson Sanger's Resume, Undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Manuscript (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Manuscript (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Page Proofs (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Page Proofs (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Paragraphs, Undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Pen Panel on Specialty Bookstores; Lynne Tillman remarks and Flier, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Research about Bookstores, 1981-1998 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Transcription Invoices, Checks, Receipts, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Series X, Subseries B: Publicity and Distribution
    - Books & Co. "Off the Wall" newsletter, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Bookstore Contacts, Reviews, Features, Promotional Events, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Panel, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Press, Publicity, and Events, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Publicity, Undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Publicity Package, Undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Reviews, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Reviews and Publicity, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Series XI: American Genius (2006)
  Series XI: American Genius contains materials related to the creation of Lynne Tillman's book "American Genius". This series includes various annotated drafts of the book, however there is no press or publicity in this series. The series is divided into one subseries:
  - Series XI, Subseries A: Drafts and Production
    - American Genius Annotated Draft (2 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Part 1 is in: Box 22, Folder 13 Part 3 is in: Box 22, Folder 27
    - American Genius Annotated Draft fragment - pages 13-165 and 62-95, Undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Gray" pages 1-115 (1 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Gray" pages 116-242 (2 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft, "Gray" pages 243-357 (3 of 3), Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft fragment pages 27-40, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft fragment pages 69-103, Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft and Notes (1 of 4), Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft and Notes pages 1-142 (2 of 4), Undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft and Notes pages 143-293 (3 of 4), Undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft and Notes pages 294-377 (4 of 4), Undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 108-213, Undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 147-183, Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 372-393, Undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - American Genius Annotated Draft Pages 385-409 and unnumbered, Undated (Box 21, Folder 15)